Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray?
Nobody knows for sure!
Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and kick away the darkness!
I'm doing this for myself,
and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
Th-These are Kaido's!
I see now!
I can take hold of them,
as I too am a dragon!
Even if I cannot push it back...
If I can at least halt it....
...or change its direction...!
If I do not do something, who will?!
Who?!
I shall save my Land of Wano!
I will not let this island
fall upon the Flower Capital!
Sparking...
...Queen!
Beams from his eyes?!
Don't tell me...!
Is everyone all right?
Yes...
Staying here is too dangerous!
Let us retreat further from here!
Chuji is gone!
Eh?
He wasn't caught
in the blast, was he...?
We must leave!
There could be another blast soon!
I...
I can't leave without him!
O-Some!
Henry...
...Queen!
Was that one of Niji's moves?
Right on the money, Vinsmoke!
Escape this!
How d'ya like them apples?!
I did thorough research
on Germa's technology!
I can copy you
'n your siblings' moves!
Would ya quit
lumping me in with them?!
I was plannin' to show 'em off
after you transformed!
If I give ya a beatdown while you're in the suit,
I could prove to Judge...
...that I'm the better scientist!
Like I friggin' care about
whatever's going on between you two!
Don't be so mean!
Winch Queen!
Bet ya felt that, didn't ya?!
I guess you were familiar
with that one, too!
My arm!
Why, you...
you damned brat!
I warned you...
Don't mention their names
in front of me!
Oh, so there's no such thing
as freedom of speech anymore?!
And another thing...
Suit or no suit,
the only thing here getting a beatdown...
...is you!
Flanchet...
...Strike!
Think you still got the upper hand?
Looks like somebody forgot
I sent 'em flying earlier...!
Pretty damn sure you felt that one!
We've been at this for a while...
You gotta be getting weaker!
Laugh at me all ya want, Queen.
I've...
...already accepted my fate.
I'm not the same guy
from back there!
Your weak ass...
...can't take me down!
How d'ya like it?
Here's your technique!
Stealth Black!
So you can do even that...
This is it!
Your backside's totally
wide open, Vinsmoke!
Wha-?! He disappeared too!
But he doesn't have the suit!
He's just movin' too fast to see!
He'll eventually run out of energy
and show himself!
What a dumb tactic!
What's with the mouse here?
Chuji!
You're all right!
Hurry, now!
We don't know when
they will start fighting again.
O-Some!
I can't believe
that tramp's still moving!
Where'd you go, Vinsmoke?
I am not Kaido's subordinate!
am just a geisha,
brought in from the Flower Capital!
O-Some! What is she doing here?!
That wench... She turned me down today,
sayin' she was laid up in bed with a headache...
But she looks full o' energy to me!
Here I was, tryin' to be all nice
'n a good customer to her,
and she gets all uppity on me! Dammit!
Playin' me for a fool!
Now that Komurasaki-tan's gone,
you're my number one!
You're not gettin' off easy...
for lying to me and turning me
down who knows how many times!
This is divine punishment!
Please let me go!
Poetic justice.
Cause and effect.
It's Johnny Obviouson!
This is punishment!
Seems like you need more pain, O-Some!
If you're still not sorry
for what you did...
What I gained...
An exoskeleton...
Muscular strength...
And mobility...
They're just extra tools in my toolbox...
By coating my exoskeleton
in finely-forged Color of Arms...
I can cover my leg in
tougher, hotter flames!
Ifrit Jambe!
More acceleration! More weight!
And the mystery is solved!
Men should never hit women!
That's been common sense
since the age of dinosaurs!
It was you, wasn't it, Queen?!
You piece of crap!
Collier!
What?! Queen-sama?!
Don't worry!
Leave him to me!
O-Okay!
Vinsmoke Sanji!
Basses Côte!
Paleron!
Jumeau à Bifteck!
Tendron!
Flanchet!
Queue!
Poire! Jarret!
Germa, Germa, Germa!
That power is so Germa!
Shut the hell up, dammit!
That name has nothing
to do with me now!
I haven't applied
my garnish to you yet!
I can turn even meat scraps
into delicious food!
Bring it on, Queen the Plague!
Shut your hole!
My science is number one in the world!
And I'm gonna wipe out
the competition all at once!
Boeuf Burst!
Lift-off, asshat!
Don't worry.
He looks unhurt.
Chuji! I'm so relieved!
He was in danger, so...
Th-Thank you!
He was making food for mice again!
Don't leave her side, now.
How's...
How's your...
...wound...
Are you all right?!
Somebody!
Bring the first-aid kit, hurry!
Our mother protected her child
at the risk of her own life,
and he was born with
the spark of humanity.
That's why you're...
...kinder than anyone else!
Battle of the Pleasure Hall,
Left-Brain Tower, Skull Dome...
Winner:
Sanji.
That's what I thought...
When the flames on his back go out,
he gets faster...
...but his defense drops!
King-sama's mask...
So the rumor was true!
Black wings, white hair, brown skin...
The Government'll give you
a hundred million berries for info!
'He's one of the mythical....
N-No, I mean...
Imperial Flaming Wings!
The castle's already burning, ya know...
You oughta try bein' a little nicer
to your underlings, if you call yourself their boss.
If they're distracting you,
why not come up here?
A hundred mil,
just for givin' the Government info?
What the hell are you, anyway?
Why ask, when you're
already a dead man?!
He's definitely a unique breed,
but what he is doesn't matter to me!
Don't got much time...
If this drags on for too long,
my sword's likely gonna be the end of me.
I see now the danger you pose.
Same to you.
Your reign's gone on long enough.
Time to clear you all
off the throne!
Don't push your luck!
Kaido-san will be the Pirate King!
Hate to tell ya,
but that ain't happenin'.
Judge of the Afterlife,
Three-Sword Style:
Purgatory...
...Demon Slash!
It was you that gave me this life...
...Kaido-san.
I see why the Government
can't let you go...
You're a Lunarian, aren't ya?
I saw the durability test earlier.
I'm gettin' out of here and
putting together a new pirate crew.
What do you wanna do,
guinea pig?
Make a not-so-fun world fun!
Choose! I'll let you decide!
Can you change...
...the world?!
I'm the only one that can!
Escaped subjects spotted!
Stop them at any cost!
I'm gonna blow their heads off!
Not much of a pursuit...
Yeah, looks that way.
Fire!
Nothing...
Our guns don't work on them!
Not too shabby!
It's nothing.
Oh, I haven't asked you!
What's your name?
Alber.
Alber! You're strong!
From now on, call yourself "King"!
King...
Stick with me, King!
I won't sell you out!
You're my right-hand man from now on!
The world needs but one king!
His flames are burning...
Attacking now is pointless!
Take this, Roronoa!
Imperial Flaming Wings!
His flames're basically magma!
Doing that again?!
You're not takin
my swords from me!
He's speedy! Which means...
...l can cut him!
Bird Dance!
Seems like you figured out...
...how I work!
That I did!
Finally caught sight
of your own defeat?
Ultra...
... Tiger Hunt!
Why're you tryin' to block?!
This ain't supposed to
work on ya, right?!
Or are you scared of my attack?!
You're biologically incapable of
defeating me!
Ain't anything I hate more in the world
than weak-ass excuses!
I'll remember you as
the bold swordsman you were....!
Lemme carve that into
your memory myself...
...if you live to
remember it, that is!
Imperial Flaming Wings!
Judge of the Afterlife,
Three-Sword Serpentine...
103 Mercies!
This is it, Roronoa!
Dragon Damnation!
K-Kaido-san...
You still think so, King?
That I'm Joyboy?
The world I'm looking to create
is the world you want?
A legend is a legend.
I don't wish for anything anymore.
You gave me the life I have now.
You must remain the strongest!
I won't lose, either...
I'll make you the Pirate King!
You won't settle for anything less than
the world's greatest swordsman, right?
Until the day I defeat him
and become a master swordsman...
I'll never... be defeated!
Got any problems with that...
Pirate King?!
Nope!
I'll become...
...the king of hell!
Battle of Right-Brain Tower,
outside the Skull Dome...
Winner:
Zoro!